[{
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 4/5?",
        "answer": "0.8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 1/2?",
        "answer": "0.5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 3/4?",
        "answer": "0.75",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 9/10?",
        "answer": "0.9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fraction form of 0.25?",
        "answer": "1/4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fraction form of 0.5?",
        "answer": "1/2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fraction form of 0.75?",
        "answer": "3/4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fraction form of 0.2?",
        "answer": "1/5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sum of 0.2 and 0.7?",
        "answer": "0.9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between 0.8 and 0.3?",
        "answer": "0.5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the product of 0.5 and 0.6?",
        "answer": "0.3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the quotient of 0.6 divided by 0.2?",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which decimal is larger: 0.45 or 0.5?",
        "answer": "0.5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which decimal is smaller: 0.7 or 0.72?",
        "answer": "0.7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 7/8?",
        "answer": "0.875",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 3/8?",
        "answer": "0.375",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 5/6?",
        "answer": "0.833",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the decimal form of 11/20?",
        "answer": "0.55",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which decimal is larger: 0.123 or 0.111?",
        "answer": "0.123",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which decimal is smaller: 0.99 or 0.999?",
        "answer": "0.99",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]